{
    "id": "20f929751f8a4c7d907c5b8cc9a543f6",
    "title": "Confusing Words Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The minister spoke of the soul’s …………………………. life.",
            "description": "Eternal means lasting forever.",
            "answers": [
                "eternal",
                "ethereal"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ff971690a33f48f6bbf693af339a8433"
        },
        {
            "question": "Her ………………………………. beauty could not be captured by the greatest painter.",
            "description": "Ethereal means celestial.",
            "answers": [
                "eternal",
                "ethereal"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1aa701c4e3f348febb370f7beb2b9db1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Her ……………………………….. would not allow her to betray a friend.",
            "description": "Ethics means moral code.",
            "answers": [
                "ethics",
                "ethnics"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a6e7097dad934dd1ac2c2ef805a20e8a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Each country has its own ……………………………… costumes.",
            "description": "Ethnic means cultural or native.",
            "answers": [
                "ethic",
                "ethnic"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "33c655cc852b4cce92a64c37cc9029b8"
        },
        {
            "question": "The politician’s …………………………….. answers infuriated the reporters.",
            "description": "Evasive means elusive or misleading.",
            "answers": [
                "evasive",
                "allusive",
                "invasive"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "32facbc5ee934d588796396cda795eb8"
        },
        {
            "question": "The procedure was only minimally …………………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "evasive",
                "invasive",
                "elusive"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f8fd1246d5d84dfaa5e4f4a284177da8"
        },
        {
            "question": "An …………………………… spends much time alone.",
            "description": "Introvert means private person.",
            "answers": [
                "introvert",
                "introspective",
                "intravert"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c9735cdeecb146f480b833cd650d7a3c"
        },
        {
            "question": "His …………………………………… sense of humor helped him through hard times.",
            "description": "Invincible means unconquerable.",
            "answers": [
                "invisible",
                "invincible",
                "invinsible"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f7b90a4d62ec49cb8a819d0cceb03c9f"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………….. romantics are always falling in love.",
            "description": "Inveterate means steadfast, diehard.",
            "answers": [
                "incorrigible",
                "die-hard",
                "inveterate",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "073d76e0c6a546a7b5e7a9b97ebce81a"
        },
        {
            "question": "In an ……………………………. position, a 9 looks like a",
            "description": "Inverted means upside down.",
            "answers": [
                "converted",
                "inverted",
                "perverted"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "06c485eec82b4f50b2dac1965e27e8c2"
        },
        {
            "question": "The sinner ……………………………….. the Lord’s forgiveness.",
            "description": "Invoke means call upon.",
            "answers": [
                "invoked",
                "evoked"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "003288fd82954bcebd28c0a0c38bde51"
        }
    ]
}